<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Android Firewall</string>
    <string name="title_enabled">Android Firewall (Firewall abilitato)</string>
    <string name="title_disabled">Android Firewall (Firewall disabilitato)</string>
    <string name="showrules">Mostra regole</string>
    <string name="applyrules">Applica regole</string>
    <string name="saverules">Salva regole</string>
    <string name="purgerules">Cancella regole</string>
    <string name="setpwd">Imposta password</string>
    <string name="help">Aiuto</string>
    <string name="close">Chiudi</string>
    <string name="exit">Esci</string>
    <string name="fw_enabled">Firewall abilitato</string>
    <string name="fw_disabled">Firewall disabilitato</string>
    <string name="log_enabled">Log abilitati</string>
    <string name="log_disabled">Log disabilitati</string>
    <string name="log_was_enabled">I log sono stati attivati</string>
    <string name="log_was_disabled">I log sono stati disattivati</string>
    <string name="ipv6_enabled">IPv6 abilitato</string>
    <string name="ipv6_disabled">IPv6 disabilitato</string>
    <string name="ipv6_was_enabled">IPv6 sono stati attivati</string>
    <string name="ipv6_was_disabled">IPv6 sono stati disattivati</string>
    <string name="log_cleared">Log svuotati</string>
    <string name="show_log">Mostra log</string>
    <string name="clear_log">Pulisci log</string>
    <string name="applying_rules">Applicazione regole iptables.</string>
    <string name="saving_rules">Salvataggio regole iptables.</string>
    <string name="deleting_rules">Eliminazione regole iptables.</string>
    <string name="rules_applied">Regole applicate con successo</string>
    <string name="rules_saved">Regole salvate con successo</string>
    <string name="rules_deleted">Regole eliminate con successo</string>
    <string name="pass_titleset">Imposta blocco password</string>
    <string name="pass_titleget">Password richiesta</string>
    <string name="enterpass">Inserisci la password:</string>
    <string name="enternewpass">Inserisci la nuova password (lascia bianco per rimuovere):</string>
    <string name="passdefined">Blocco password definito</string>
    <string name="passremoved">Blocco password rimosso</string>
    <string name="passerror">Errore cambiamento blocco password</string>
    <string name="working">Attendere...</string>
    <string name="reading_apps">Lettura applicazioni installate</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Attendi perfavore</string>
    <string name="mode_header">Modo: %s</string>
    <string name="mode_whitelist">White list (abilita selezionati)</string>
    <string name="mode_blacklist">Black list (blocca selezionati)</string>
    <string name="toast_bin_installed">Android Firewall: File binari installati!</string>
    <string name="toast_enabled">Android Firewall: Firewall abilitato!</string>
    <string name="toast_error_enabling">Android Firewall: Errore di abilitazione firewall!</string>
    <string name="toast_disabled">Android Firewall: Firewall disabilitato!</string>
    <string name="toast_error_disabling">Android Firewall: Errore di disabilitare firewall!</string>
    <string name="overwrite_rules">Stai per sovrascrivere le norme vigenti. Vuoi continuare?</string>
    <string name="importsuccess">Importazione di successo!</string>
    <string name="importfailed">Importazione non riuscita!</string>
    <string name="exportfailed">Export fallito!</string>
    <string name="exportsuccess">Esportazione di successo!</string>
    <string name="enterfilename">Inserisci il nome del file</string>
    <string name="notify_enabled">Notifiche abilitato</string>
    <string name="notify_disabled">Notifiche disattivato</string>
    <string name="notify_was_enabled">Le notifiche sono stati abilitati</string>
    <string name="notify_was_disabled">Le notifiche sono state disattivate</string>
    <string name="importrules">importare le regole</string>
    <string name="exportrules">Regole di esportazione</string>
    <string name="managerulefiles">Gestione dei file delle regole</string>
    <string name="options">Opzioni</string>
    <string name="wifi">WiFi</string>
    <string name="data">dati</string>
    <string name="roaming">Roam</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="password_not_same">Le password non sono uguali! Si prega di riprovare.</string>
    <string name="password_enter_again">Inserisci di nuovo la password.</string>
    <string name="defaultprofile">Default</string>
    <string name="profile1">Profilo 1</string>
    <string name="profile2">Profilo 2</string>
    <string name="profile3">Profilo 3</string>
    <string name="profile4">Profilo 4</string>
    <string name="profile5">Profilo 5</string>
    <string name="pleasechoose">Si prega di selezionare il profilo che si desidera creare o modificare</string>
    <string name="saveprofile">Crea il tuo profilo</string>
    <string name="defaultsaved">Il profilo predefinito è stato salvato con successo!</string>
    <string name="profile1saved">Profilo 1 è stato salvato con successo</string>
    <string name="profile2saved">Profilo 2 è stato salvato con successo</string>
    <string name="profile3saved">Profilo 3 è stato salvato con successo</string>
    <string name="profile4saved">Profilo 4 è stato salvato con successo</string>
    <string name="profile5saved">Profilo 5 è stato salvato con successo</string>
    <string name="profileselect">Si prega di scegliere il profilo che si desidera applicare</string>
    <string name="profileapplied">Il profilo è stato applicato con successo</string>
    <string name="loadprofile">Carica profilo</string>
    <string name="rulesoptions">Rules Management</string>
    <string name="profilesoptions">Profile Management</string>
    <string name="ipv6_title">IPv6 Support</string>
    <string name="notifications_title">Notifica di supporto</string>
    <string name="enableLog_title">Enable Firewall Log</string>
    <string name="invert">Invert</string>
    <string name="twofortyfouram_locale_breadcrumb_format">%1$s%2$s%3$s</string>
    <string name="twofortyfouram_locale_breadcrumb_separator">" | "</string>
    <string name="twofortyfouram_locale_menu_dontsave">Cancel</string>
    <string name="twofortyfouram_locale_menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="twofortyfouram_locale_menu_save">Done</string>
    <string name="tasker_name">Android Firewall - Tasker</string>
    <string name="tasker_profile_disabled">Android Firewall profiles changed by Tasker. Firewall disabled!</string>
    <string name="search_name">App Search</string>
    <string name="profilenames">Edit nomi dei profili</string>
    <string name="vpn_enabled">Supporto VPN è stato abilitato</string>
    <string name="vpn_disabled">Supporto VPN è stato disattivato</string>
    <string name="vpn_title">Supporto VPN</string>
    <string name="vpn">VPN</string>
    <string name="roaming_title">Roaming Supporto</string>
    <string name="usersettings">Impostazioni</string>
    <string name="taskertoast_title">Tasker Notifiche</string>
    <string name="ipv6_summary">Questa impostazione abilita o disabilita il supporto IPv6</string>
    <string name="vpn_summary">Questa impostazione abilita o disabilita il supporto VPN</string>
    <string name="roaming_summary">Questa impostazione abilita o disabilita Il Roaming supporto di rete</string>
    <string name="taskertoast_summary">Questa impostazione abilita o disabilita Tasker notifica pop-up quando i profili sono cambiati</string>
    <string name="log_summary">Questa impostazione abilita o disabilita del firewall i log</string>
    <string name="notification_summary">Questa impostazione consente di attivare o disattivare le notifiche per le applicazioni di nuova installazione che richiedono l\'accesso a Internet</string>
    <string name="tasker_profile">Tasker è cambiato il profilo in uso da Android Firewall</string>
    <string name="apply_setting_changes">Applicando norme relative alla fissazione cambia</string>
    <string name="rules_export_successfully">Le regole siano state esportate con successo</string>
    <string name="rules_import_successfully">Le regole siano stati importati con successo</string>
    <string name="no_rules_file">Vi è un errore di accesso alla directory androidfirewall. Si prega di esportare un file di regole prima</string>
    <string name="no_storage">Vi è un errore di accesso alla directory androidfirewall. Si prega di verificare che la SDcard è montata o di archiviazione esterna è accessibile.</string>
    <string name="file_deleted">Il file è stato eliminato.</string>
    <string name="simplewidget">On/Off Widget</string>
    <string name="statuswidget">Menu Widget</string>
    <string name="sdcard_title">Apps on SDCard Support</string>
    <string name="sdcard_summary">This setting makes the app wait for the SDCard scan to be finished before applying rules after reboot.  This is needed if you have apps that require data access and you moved them to the SDCard.  Please note that this increases the time it takes for the rules to be applied after a reboot.</string>
    <string name="lan">LAN</string>
    <string name="lan_summary">This setting enables or disables LAN support.  This allows an app access to your LAN but not the Internet.</string>
    <string name="lan_title">LAN Support</string>
    <string name="select_mode">Select mode:</string>
    <string name="delete_rules_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="delete_rules_no">No</string>
    <string name="no_rules_files">There is an error accessing the androidfirewall directory. Please export a rules file first.</string>
    <string name="no_storage">There is an error accessing the androidfirewall directory. Please check that your SDcard is mounted or external storage is accessible.</string>
    <string name="rules_file_deleted">The file has been deleted.</string>
    <string name="version_about">Version:</string>
    <string name="help_usage"><b>Using Android Firewall</b>\n<b>1.</b> Click on <b>Mode</b> to switch between <i>White List</i> and <i>Black List</i> modes.
\n<b>2.</b> Mark the applications that you want to block or allow (depending on the selected mode), for each interface.
\n<b>3.</b> Open the menu and enable the firewall. If the firewall is already enabled, just select <b>Apply rules</b>.
\nThe rules will be saved and automatically restored when you restart your phone.
\nIf you want to check all current iptables rules, select <b>Show rules</b> from the Navigation Drawer.
\n
\n<b>Widgets</b>\nTo quickly enable or disable the firewall with a single touch, add the On/Off Widget to your home screen.
\nTo quickly change profiles or enable/disable the firewall, add the Menu Widget to your home screen.
\n
\n<b>Firewall logs</b>\nIf you want to see which applications have been blocked by Android Firewall, open the <i>Settings</i> menu and enable the Log.
\nAndroid Firewall will then log each application blocked. You can check the log by opening the menu and selecting <b>Show log</b> from the Navigation Drawer.
\n
\n<b>Password lock</b>\nYou can set a password lock for Android Firewall by using the <b>Set password</b> option in the Navigation Drawer.
\nTo remove the password protection, just reset it to blank.
\n
\n<b>App search</b>\nYou can search for a specific app by typing the first few letters of the apps name in the search bar next to the spinner.
\n
\n<b>Supported Interfaces</b>\nAlong side the traditional WiFi and Data interfaces, three other interfaces are now supported.  Support for VPNs, Roaming, and LANs are avaiable.  These are enabled under <i>Settings</i>.
\n
\n<i>VPN support</i> allows apps to only access the data stream when connected to a VPN.
\n<i>Roaming support</i> allows apps to access the data stream when you are roaming.
\n<i>LAN support</i> allows apps to access LAN data but not the Internet.
\n
\n<b>Tasker/Locale Support</b>\n<i>Android Firewall</i> contains a plugin for Tasker and Locale.  The plugin allows those apps to Enable or Disable the firewall and change profiles based on different variables.  For more information please read the Tasker instructions under the Profiles Help tab.
\nNotifications from Tasker stating changes have been made to the firewall are disabled by default.  They can be enabled under <i>Settings</i>.
\n
\n<b>Other settings</b>\n
\nIPv6 support is available under <i>Settings</i> for those who use IPv6.
\nUsers can change the apps language to one of the supported languages under <i>Settings</i>.
\nSDcard support for users who have moved apps to their SDcard.  Please read the setting description before enabling.
\n
\n<b>Information</b>\n
\n<i>Media Server</i> is <b>required</b> for <i>YouTube</i> to function.
\n
\n<i>Tethering</i> requires <b>(root) - applications running as root</b> and <b>Kernel</b>.  Please use your profiles to quickly enable/disable those rules.</string>
    <string name="help_rules"><i>Rules Management</i> is the ability to export, import, and delete rules files.\n  
        \nAll user preferences are stored in the rules file so when you export a rules file you also save your Settings like notification support, log enabled, IPv6 support, and the rest.  These files are used to create your profiles as well.
\n
\n<b>Export Rules</b> exports your current rules and settings.
\n<b>Import Rules</b> imports rules and settings from a file.
\n<b>Manage Rule Files</b> allows you to delete rules files.
\n
\n<i><b>Instructions</b></i>\n
\n<b>Export Rules</b>	\n
\n1.  Swipe left to open the Navigation Drawer.
\n2.  Touch <i>Export Rules</i>.
\n3.  Enter a name for the export files.
\n4.  Touch OK to save the file.
\n
\nThe file is stored on whatever your device considers its external storage in a folder named <i>androidfirewall</i>.  The file name is the user entered name and \'_af.rules\' appended to the end.
\n
\n<b>Import Rules</b>	\n
\n1.  Swipe left to open the Navigation Drawer.
\n2.  Touch <i>Import Rules</i>.
\n3.  Touch the rules file you want to import.
\n
\nAfter you touch the rules file you want to import, the data is imported and firewall settings are changed and rules applied.
\n
\n<b>Manage Rule Files</b>	\n
\n1.  Swipe left to open the Navigation Drawer.
\n2.  Touch <i>Manage Rule Files</i>.
\n3.  Touch the rules file you want to delete.
\n4.  You will receive a dialog box to confirm the deletion.
\n5.  Touch \'No\' or \'Yes\'.  
\n
\nIf you touch \'Yes\' the rules file is deleted.</string>
    <string name="help_profiles"><i>Profiles</i> are used to quickly change the firewall rules and settings.  This is a very powerful tool as you may want a totally different set of rules depending on where you are or what network you are on.  For example, when at work your rules may be very different compared to when you are home.
\n
\nProfiles are created from rules files that you have exported so you can swap between them quickly and easily if you ever need more than 5 profiles.\n
\n<b>Create Profile</b> allows you to choose a rules file and assign those rules and settings to a profile.
\n<b>Load Profile</b> allows you to apply a profile.
\n<b>Edit Profile Names</b> allows you to edit the names of the profiles in order to make it easier to remember what profile does what.
\n
\nYou can swap profiles in a variety of different ways:
\n
\n<b>1.</b> Manually load a profile by using Load Profile.
\n<b>2.</b> Load a profile by using the dropdown spinner on the main app screen.
\n<b>3.</b> Use an app like Tasker or Locale to automatically change the profile based on time, location, or some other variable you choose.
\n<b>4.</b> Use the <i>Menu Widget</i> to quickly change profiles from your homescreen.
\n
\n<i><b>Instructions</b></i>\n
\n<b>Create Profile</b>\n
\n1.  Swipe left to open the Navigation Drawer.
\n2.  Touch <i>Create Profile</i>.
\n3.  Touch the profile you wish to create.
\n4.  Touch the rules file you want assigned to that profile.
\n5.  Touch another profile if you want to assign another rules files otherwise hit the back key.
\n
\n<b>Load Profile</b>\n
\n1.  Swipe left to open the Navigation Drawer.
\n2.  Touch <i>Load Profile</i>.
\n3.  Touch the profile you wish to apply.
\n
\n<b>Edit Profile Names</b>\n
\n1.  Swipe left to open the Navigation Drawer.
\n2.  Touch <i>Edit Profile Names</i>.
\n3.  Touch the profile you want to rename.
\n4.  Enter the name for the profile and touch \'OK\'.
\n5.  Continue modifying the names otherwise hit the back key.
\n
\n<b>Using the Spinner</b>\n
\n1.  Touch the spinner and a drop down with all the profiles appears.
\n2.  Touch the profile you wish to load.
\n
\n<b>Using Tasker</b>\n
\n1.  Open Tasker.
\n2.  Touch the \'+\' and select the \'First Context\' for what will cause the profile change.
\n3.  After you done setting up your context you will be prompted to \'Enter Task\'.
\n4.  Enter a name for the task if you desire then touch the checkmark.
\n5.  Touch the \'+\' and a \'Select Action Category\' screen appears.
\n6.  Touch \'Plugin\'.
\n7.  Touch <i>Android Firewall</i>.
\n8.  Touch the \'Edit\' button.
\n9.  Select which profile you want Tasker to apply.
\n10.  Hit the back key once. You may now test the Tasker profile by touching the \'Play\' button in the bottom left corner.</string>
    <string name="help_dialog_text"><i>Author: Jason Tschohl.  Original Author: Rodrigo Zechin Rosauro</i>		\n    <i><a href="http://github.com/skullone/android_firewall">http://github.com/skullone/android_firewall</a></i>		\n
		\n    <i>Android Firewall</i> is a fork of     <i>DroidWall</i> which is a front-end application for the powerful     <b>iptables</b> Linux firewall.
		It allows you to restrict which applications are permitted to access your data networks.\n
		\nThis is the perfect solution if you don\'t have an unlimited data plan or care about your privacy.\n
		\n
		\n  </string>

</resources>